Oh,
hello.  hmm.
wait a minute.  I'll take a ride on the Mega Village in the water
.  Yes.
Ah, ah, I'm a little late today because I went to the field
.
Yes.  hmm.   Just
a moment.
Hello, Mr. Go.  Oh, yes.  There
was a bit of an unplanned problem.  Are you starting from that field
?  Your hair
is really long too.  Hello LG.   I
need to start by cutting my hair
.  hmm.  yes.
Oh, if you come back in about 5 more minutes, we
can talk to you, and there are many people waiting for you to raise the calves and
milk them, so please just wait
a moment.  Let me tidy up my microphone cable
.  yes.
If you come in a little later in about five minutes,
I'll tell you then.  Oh anyway,
sleep for a bit.
Oh, my
hair.
Since I'm working, I
don't really get to get my hair cut anymore, but I think
I should cut it a little short before I start.
I
got a perm, but if
I cut it again, it'll all disappear, and I'm
wondering what I should do with my hair
.  I used to do karma po before,
but of course now I just don't dry it and
it's hot.  Hello Melky, what should I do next
[music]?
Can I show you some pictures?
Oh, I didn't take a picture, but I
think I have one.  yes.  Well,
there were things that went well and things that felt good,
but there were also some things that were a bit
critical, so I'll tell
you about them one by one. First of all,
it was last Saturday, Saturday, March 29th.
I
got some help from Deulpan, Binerin Deulpan, and Gimcheon Durumi, and we've
almost finished moving
.  At that time, when I moved, the
most difficult thing was that I
had a photo truck, so I could load most things onto it and
move them like this, but I
couldn't move things like refrigerators by myself, even though I had the space
.  So now,
Bineridul came all the way here to help with that part, and
Yorom-nim was in Gimcheon
so he gave us his time, but the distance
wasn't that bad.  hmm.  yes.  Anyway, so
now I decided to get help moving the refrigerator,
but
now I ca
n't just move it, I have to buy another one
.  So I've been going into Carrot Market for a while and I
've been working hard on carrot porridge.
Well, Gimcheon is a bit
smaller and there are
n't many people using carrots for various reasons, so there are
n't many properties for sale here. So, last year,
Gumi
was a much larger city that was relatively close to Gimcheon.  hmm.   It was
a bit much to go all the way to Daegu, so I
bought a refrigerator in Gumi. Deulpa-nim,
Bine Deulpa-nim is
coming from the metropolitan area near Suwon, so
there is Daejeon on the way.  So I thought it would be a good idea to meet in Daejeon,
buy a refrigerator on a truck, and
head straight to the field
.   On
my way back from Seoul last time, I went to Daejeon and got a
neighborhood certification and searched for it diligently.
So I found something that I thought was pretty good
.  Refrigerator Home Power Refrigerator
It's about 10 years old, I think it was a 2014 model,
yes, I bought it for 50,000 won.
I think it was around 780L.  Is there a picture of that too?
wait a minute.  I think I took some pictures of the refrigerators,
but they're nothing special,
right?  Oh, I think I deleted the screenshot I took
.  Oh, this is a bit
disappointing.  yes.  Anyway, and there are these huge refrigerators in the store that are
made of 45 boxes of commercial refrigerators
.  At first
I thought about doing that, but since it's a cold storage type,
those types of refrigerators are really
expensive.  But since I keep
moving around and can't use it in one place for a long time,
I've been
buying it cheaply on Carrot Market like I used to, and it's cheaper again,
so I carry it lightly when I move, and when I
move to a new place, I
buy it again at the place I work at. I think that's better, and I do
n't really like buying it expensively,
so I've given up on that
.  Instead, I bought another beverage refrigerator
.  Oh, hello, Jeje,
Kwon In-ah, Merbuba, and Paling
.
Yes, the pen on top of the Suneung Growth Engine continues to
spin powerfully, generating a lot of heat and
consuming a lot of electricity, but the
cooling performance is much better, so
when you first extract the milk and need to cool it down quickly, there is nothing like it
.  Well,
since we don't have a situation where we can use rapid freezers or anything like that, we have them all together in the field and at
home,
so we squeeze them in the field and put them right there,
and then after feeding and watering the cows, we take them
out of the refrigerator,
come home, divide them into small portions, and then
refrigerate them again, and that's how we
did it. But now, if there's a
lot of oil left, or if we store it later, there
might not be enough storage space
.  For various reasons,
I wanted to have one more refrigerator than last year, and yes.  In that respect, I
thought it would be better to just buy another beverage refrigerator with good cooling performance, so I
bought one of those.  The
home refrigerator and home power
refrigerator, which are almost the same size as last year, will now store items that have
cooled down in the beverage refrigerator that cools quickly
.   I
bought it for 50,000 won, 100,000 won, a
beverage refrigerator for 100,000 won, and a carrot for
50,000
won. As long as it
doesn't break, I think it will be useful.   It would be
good if you could just endure it for a little while
.
Hello, Dad.  yes.  Anyway, I
made a good purchase and had a good time with Deulpa, but I
was a bit worried that it would be difficult to load.
Ah, this refrigerator is a bit
heavy and we do
n't have the technology to do it, so we were a bit worried, but
fortunately, the whole process from
moving the refrigerator, buying it from the Carrot Market place,
loading it into the car, and
then
unloading it and putting it in my house
was really smooth and easy.  More than I thought.  So,
up to that point, it was really good.   The
person selling the refrigerator there
happened to be doing it on the day we were buying a new one, so
while we were fumbling around,
the refrigerator installers came and
said they would take it down themselves, but since they
were technicians, it
was completely different.  We were
having a really hard time, wondering what to do with this,
and we were just lying on the floor and
doing weird things, and then these guys just
came in with a cart that was just the right size for the hallway and stuff, and they
put the wheels under the refrigerator and just
dragged it around in one go.
They just passed by as if nothing happened, like the chin or something. So they helped me and
brought it to the front of the car, but
if they had to load it there, of course it
wasn't a big deal. And when I got it out later, the
door of my old house, the house I lived in last year, was so small and cramped, and
there was a shoe rack, so it
was incredibly difficult.  Tae-nim and I were putting it in and it
was really hard. We
had a really hard time. And
after putting the refrigerator in the house, the
refrigerator was also big, so we had to
put it back in the room where it was over 800L, but the
door was too small. So, to put it in, we had to take the
door off, but just taking the door off wasn't enough. We had to
take off the iron that was holding the door, and the
handle on the back of the refrigerator, and we
had to take off all this and that, but it
wasn't easy to take it off, and we
needed tools. We had to go and buy tools
.  But this time, I did
n't have to take anything off, and the door was so wide that I could just go
in and put it in, and that was
it.  It
was so good.  yes.
There was no need to go through the small door, and when you just
opened the front door,
there was something like a living room
.  yes.  And then it just
got twisted right away.  So, until then, I was really
happy about moving this time, and as I was
moving to Daejeok and stuff, I
thought about working last year and
felt really good.  Oh, but
there's one thing I've already heard to some extent back then.  That's a little bit different,
but the landowner called me and
said that he was going to do this and that, so this is actually the
biggest debt I have on the field I'm currently renting.  Now,
there is a large field called Guak, and
the hut that is built on that large field is
quite
large, about 6*6m, and it
seems like it could be a bit bigger
.  actually.  And since it won't be enough to
just do that around there anyway, I
'm going to build a net on a piece of land that's about 10m x 10m.
But it's a bit weird to tell them not to do something,
and in fact, they
didn't even ask for my opinion.  So
I said I understood, but this time they're going to
build a house in front of that hut
.  So, he said he was going to build his own house and do this and
that, but when would he be able to
move in?
I think the landlord said he would help me move now because he wanted to ask me to help him build the house.  But I just
tried to gloss over it and
let it go, but now the
head of the household called me and said that
my vice principal had been blown away by the wind
.  So the vice principal
is looking down at the ceiling.  So, it's a 180 degree
turn
.  Oh, but actually,
I actually experienced a typhoon when a typhoon was coming, so
how could this have come when it didn't fly away when that typhoon was coming
?
Should I say that I am half-believing and half-doing it?  And even
though I was hearing that kind of story, I was in a
really good mood until then, and
because I was jealous of that typhoon, I
had to go anyway, so I
went to the field with Deulmi and Deulpa to ask them to help me set it up.  I went to see and it was actually there
.  180 degrees. I don't know how
it turned out like that, but it's probably because the wind
was so strong that it ended up like this
.  The vice principal.
So, it looks like the wind blew and it floated like this and
really swung like this.
So, since it was down on the ground like this,
the roof was completely destroyed
and it
seemed like it needed to be rebuilt, so I
ordered a new roofing material.  Well,
that's something that'll take a day or so, no,
not even a day, but a few hours
to fix, so I
think I can get it and fix it tomorrow.
And as he was going over, he fell over the
fence and one side of the fence
collapsed.  That was it, but
I already paid for that.
Up until that point, it was natural,
so I thought, "Oh, that's how it
went," and now,
through the next pot, I'm going to park, but
something feels unusual
.
Looking at this, I found out later that
there were many problems.  First of all,
if we really want to talk about the really important amount, there
is one large field, and
then his Junhwa, so although it
is not that big, there are one or two other large amounts that are about half the size of the large field
.  But in one of those places, the landowner
brought in a forklift and dug up the
center and one end like this, saying that he was digging a water well
.  Dig two lines like this
and
connect one side to the existing waterway. Dig one side like this.
But last year, the landowner said he
wanted to do this, so if you
do it like this, the water will drain well.  I just
need to get some water out.  I
told him that I was in a position where I had to drive the vice principal around, and that if there was a big hole in the middle, the car wouldn't be able to drive, so I
told him that it wouldn't work. But when I asked the landowner later, he said that he didn't know anything.  I
don't quite understand, but anyway, I don't know if he
just can't remember or
what it was like, but he
said he wouldn't do it last year, but now he's
doing it without asking me
.  In the middle, they just
dug up the ground with a forklift.  Oh, so now it's
become a bit difficult for cars to get in there.  The car has to pull the next truck, but
that has become a bit
ambiguous, and now
there is a lot of land that is just being abandoned.  Well, the
abandoned land actually has a really effective water path,
and if the water
drains well, maybe the grass can grow a little better
.  During the rainy season in the summer,
that's something to be watched for,
but aside from that, cars couldn't enter,
so one field was destroyed like that
.  And now, while doing that,
and building a house on top of that, and
clearing the ground and things like that, and with the
forklifts and heavy equipment
going back and forth,
a lot of fences were destroyed, and also, I
don't know what kind of wind came in, but
since they cut down the side of the mountain and made fields,
there are slopes here and there.  There's a field, a
slope, a field, and things like that, and they
just took the trees on the slope and
cut them down to make electric fields
.  So these trees just
fell down and covered my fence
.  So the fences were all
torn down
.
So, the chainsaw cut down the trees
and the fence was destroyed, and the heavy equipment was
now touching the fence again and uprooting it and
destroying it all, and the land was filled with dirt, and they were
going to build a house in front of the hut in that large field, and it
took up a lot more space than I thought.  So
now the large field area there has
been reduced a lot and there have been a lot of problems here and there.
Well, I
went to the landowner and saw it and I was so shocked
and embarrassed, and as I was going there, I heard the sound of a car and got
a call.  When I called and
asked about it, they said that they didn't do it last year and that
digging the waterway wouldn't work and that cars wouldn't be able to
get in. When I
asked why, they said that they told me to stir it so that the water would drain better,
but this is what happened, so I told them that I
clearly told them that last year and they were
really upset and said that they would
fill it up again
.  But if you already dug up all the black, you'll have
to dig up the surrounding land again and do this to fill it up.
So, I think it needs to be filled in,
but I
wanted to see how the land has changed since I've been grazing without training the land for three years now and using a regenerative farming method. Of course,
there are some lands that haven't been touched,
but among them,
one of the most important parts has been
dug up like that, and now they're saying that they have to fill it
in and cover the rest next to it and
make it roughly sloped,
and that's also a bit annoying. And once they
dig it all up with a forklift, it does
n't look like any other land next to it.
When it rains, it hardens even more and now
it's practically like it's been dug up
.  So, all the
hard work I put in over the years, two years' worth of hard work, just
ended up as a parcel.
Yeah, that was something like that too.  And the
fence
was all broken, so I asked what happened, and
oh, that's what happened.   It was
like this.  That's what happened.
So, what happened
that day, when I first called him, he was
really upset
and said he would take care of everything and
stuff like that, so I
hung up the phone.  But
since we couldn't talk for long back then, those
people who came to help me have
left, and I
talked to them again yesterday.
So, that
gentleman said he would give us 80,000 won if we helped him build his house
.  So he came and told me to
do some back hair too.  So, I
started working like this and
brought the cow right away,
so the plan was to bring the cow this week
.  I
was planning to bring the cows right away and start right away
so that I can start making money as soon as possible, but
now that the fence is all torn down, I have
to start repairing it.
Why on earth are you doing that?  So
why are you making me feel sorry?  So,
this is a really different way of thinking
.  Oh, so this conversation has been the
same since before, but I
had always thought that he was not my god,
but he said he would help me.  I
'll help you.  That
doesn't take long.  I'm just saying, "I'll
bring a tractor and help you."  So,
he said that there was no need for a track and that this wasn't something that could be done with equipment, but something that had to be done directly by a person, so he offered to help and said, "Why are you making people feel bad?" and then he did the opposite.
Ah, anyway, because of that, ah, but
still, it was like that yesterday,
it was like that today, and now, probably
tomorrow, the roofing materials will
arrive.  It
was the weekend the day before yesterday, so I'll probably leave today and
have it delivered tomorrow
.  yes.  Then, tomorrow, I'm going to repair the roof material
connection and make the gutter usable, and then
I'm going to repair the lower part and
bring the cows to the field that hasn't been destroyed first,
and while the cows are there, I'm going to
do some work, and then I'm going to spend
more time diligently doing the repairs above at the
same time.  Bringing cows and
doing cow work, and now in my spare time, I
repair the fence, fill in some of the broken ground, and supervise a bit, and I
need to do a good job of doing this so that the rest can go up again.
So, for now, we are trying to proceed quickly with that plan
so that there are no disruptions to the original plan
.  So I'm planning to
call back tomorrow to see if I can buy some cattle right away,
and yes.   I'm
not sure what will happen.  Well, I'm
thinking of doing that for now,
and I've already applied for internet at the house I'm moving into, and the
technician will come tomorrow to install it,
and I have to move there too.
Anyway, it's becoming a bit difficult
.  The trial is on April 14th,
so there will be a lot of things to do with that.
But the landowner is causing a fuss,
so what can we do?   I have to
try hard
.  yes.  Anyway,
there were some things like that.  So I was
a bit out of it and of course I
forgot about the mic yesterday,
but I couldn't turn on the broadcast yesterday
.  How far did I go in greeting you
?  Hello, Yu Ji-hyun, Choi, Ah,
Choi, Okay, Jeogai,
Owl, and Low.
Hello, Jeong Ui-gyeong, Dumbi, Gangsub Gwanjeodong, Shin Woong-dong, and Ann.
Nice to meet you.  Yes, I do
n't think I can leave without listening to the live, so I'll just leave a question
.  If I
mix honey with hot water and drink it, will it get heated? Is that
bad?  And I was wondering if you have any recommendations for
Kebal Honey
?
Ah, first of all, the biggest reason I recommend eating raw fish
is probably because of the living enzymes.  hmm.  Hot water or warm water
would be okay, but if you
put it in literally hot water, especially boiling water, or
whatever, it doesn't have to be boiling water, and if
it's over 50 degrees, it
'll probably be destroyed to some extent.  In that context, I don't think it's a good idea to put the raw fish
in water that's too hot
.  Rather than saying it's not good, there's
no reason to eat raw honey like that anymore
.  Because it's going to heat up anyway
.
I think it would be better to just buy 6-stage honey.  Well, it
's a bit difficult to say specifically because it depends on each person's personal taste, and
foreign organic products are often cheaper than domestic ones,
so yes.  I think it would be good to look for
organic raw bones and buy them from places like Coupang or Iub. For
cooking, you can just buy organic ones that are cheap,
regardless of whether they are sterilized or frozen
.
Hello hj.
Hello sir.  If I take deworming medication,
will it harm my gut microbiome?  Oh,
that could be
possible.  But anyway, I'm going to take some deworming medicine anyway
.  And I don't think there's any need to take deworming medication for no
reason
.  hmm.
Yeah, yeah.
So, unless
there is something definite about the actual infection in some other sense,
like I
saw it with my own eyes or
something like that, and even for
that, you should go to the hospital and talk about it,
and since albendazole
won't solve the problem anyway, you
may need to get a prescription for Prazitel or something else, and
so on
.  yes.  Well, unless you just go to the hospital and the
doctor prescribes Prazite or
tells you to take Albender,
or if a blood test or
other test
suggests a parasitic infection, I'm
not sure.  I don't think you really need to eat
it, but even
if you do eat it, it's just a short deworming pill and it's not a lot,
so I don't think you need to worry too much
.
Hello, Hong Young-joo.  Hello, Aja.   I have
repeatedly read in many books that it is bad for you to eat meat if you have the A4 gene.  How
should I interpret this?
I know there's nothing wrong with consuming vitality, but I
don't know how to refute such claims.  Well, I
don't remember the exact details, but
A4 is it, so as far as I know, it
's probably related to Alchimer in modern times.
Shall we take a quick look?
Yes, here's what the Google AI dog
is telling us these days.  Alzheimer's disease is one of the
strongest genetic risk factors for dementia, as it increases the risk of dementia
.
hmm.  yes.
Anyway, that gene is called a risk factor that you should
definitely have for dementia these days, but
in fact,
it's not all bad.  Of course, if
that were all bad, I would have been the only one who
didn't have it in the long history of human evolution, and
everyone who had it would
have been eliminated and disappeared.  But despite that,
I think it's the
gene that increases parasite resistance that has continued to this day and increases the risk of Alchimera in modern people.
So, in modern times, it
only has bad aspects, but for ancient humans who were rife with parasitic infections, it
was a kind of thankful gene that gave us the additional strength to endure parasitic infections.   It
used to be a beneficial gene,
but in modern times, the risk of parasites has
practically disappeared,
especially for Koreans living in the 21st century
.  yes.  As a result, only the
bad aspects are highlighted
.  But as far as I know, the
so-called dementia risk that is said to be a bad thing is
only true when there is insulin resistance,
and as for the children, I have seen
it before, so what I am saying now is not 100%
accurate.  If I may
just speak from my memory, I believe that
when you have insulin sensitivity, the
risk of developing Alzheimer's increases, so if you
eat a healthy diet such as a curry or a low-carb diet, there may be some
remnants of the past parasite resistance that
remain, but I
understand that it has nothing to do with the risk of dementia.
Well, it has nothing to do with meat in the first place
.  Well, I think that's why most people think that
eating meat increases insulin sensitivity
.  That's why there are people who claim that if you eat raw fish, you'll
get diabetes, and that if you eat that meat, you'll
get diabetes.
yes.  Now,
people who develop diabetes and insulin resistance,
especially those who have that gene, are
more likely to suffer from Alzheimer's, or
Alzheimer itself is also
called diabetes.
When the brain experiences insulin resistance, it can progress to Alzheimer's disease
.  yes.  So,
in that context, I think it's probably because the enemy's vitality is not good
.  But actually, red meat has
nothing to do with diabetes, and
if you think about it, a cannibalistic diet is very harmful to diabetes, then
I don't think there's anything to worry about.
Oh, come to think of it, the photo I
took earlier was, ah, I was looking at it earlier, and I was
busy clearing away the tree and fixing the broken fence, and I
just took a moment to sigh and take a photo
.  I'll just
go ahead and show you this one.  Well, I've
already
told you everything anyway.  yes.
There were a lot of bigger trees, but they
just
cut down the trees on the slopes like this.  Oh, but I really
wonder if people can be like this.  That other
person, that is, the person who knows that the person who came into his field
built a fence to kill him,
just cuts it down like this so that
all the trees fall and the fence is
destroyed like this. I think that's a really
different way of thinking
.  I really
don't understand the actual Jehangsikseon.
But what can I do?
yes.
What can I do?  I
have to do that because it's not something I can do.
hmm.  Since traditional groups of people
ate a lot of this product and still had few cavities,
can we assume that lactose does not cause cavities?
Sugar doesn't cause cavities in the first place
.  I think you're right to think that way
.  Cavities
do not occur because of eating sugar.
Cavities are fundamentally caused by a lack of fat-soluble vitamins and
minerals
.  Fat-soluble vitamins Conversely, if you consume enough fat-soluble
vitamins and minerals, you will
not get cavities even if you eat a lot of food.  Not only did they eat the toppings, but the
people of Lesintal also ate a lot of homemade bread
.  They were people who lived on hoe,
and people who lived in Scotland also
lived on oats, so they also
ate a lot of sugar.   I
don't know if you want to see it as different from lactose, glucose, or starch, but anyway,
since amylase is produced in the mouth, whether you
eat bread, oats, or rye, when you
eat these kinds of offerings, they
become glucose and
remain in the mouth.  But those things
don't cause cavities.  Yes, in the first place, nutritional deficiency
causes cavities,
so
yes, that's right.
no see.  Do you have a separate account other than Super Chat
?  I
don't remember my account details from yesterday
.  If you look at the Cafe 24 Supernatural Animals
website, there is an account that leads to a bank transfer
.  yes.
Hello, couple.  It's been a little over a year since I started Canive
.  I was diagnosed with spinal arthritis about a month ago
.
Can Cannibalism help improve symptoms?
Oh, but you were
diagnosed about a month ago after following the diet for a year.
So, you were continuing the diet, and the
fact that you developed spinal arthritis in the meantime means that you were continuing the diet and that the
diet was good. So, if we
assume that you were following the diet well,
then to put it
simply,
if Carnivora is a diet that causes spinal arthritis, then you
need to change the Carnivora itself. But if Carnivora is
not related to spinal arthritis
or you think that it is a good diet that helps with healing, then the
fact that you developed spinal arthritis while continuing Carnivora
means that there are other variables.
Wouldn't it depend on what caused the spinal arthritis?
So, if what I do is something
like loading and unloading parcels, and that
puts a lot of strain on my spine and
causes arthritis, then of
course I should change my diet, but it would be much more important to stop doing
things that put a lot of strain on my spine while doing that loading and unloading work.
So, I think there must be another real reason, and I
think you should take care of that part first.
How should I do the ritual diet?
I want to go on a diet without any extra time.  Actually, this is a very simple
problem.  In general, yes.
So of course, there may
be some differences in detail for each person, but to
put it in general terms,
eat a lot of meat to
provide sufficient nutrients, and also provide sufficient nutrients to internal organs and such, and
eat relatively less energy sources such as fat, and exercise
consistently to increase muscle mass and
do strength training consistently, and of course,
for cardiopulmonary endurance,
so if you go this way, you
have to do all the things that are good for your health.  But in fact,
rather than the purpose of dieting and losing weight itself, the
things I'm talking about now, or the
things you see in these examples,
are fundamentally for creating a healthy body, and
since a healthy body is not a fat body, you
can think of it as closer to losing weight automatically once you have a healthy body.  If your goal is to lose weight,
then actually, as you said, you
want a diet without urination, but
if you don't care about urination, you
will definitely lose weight if you just starve yourself.  There are 50,000 different diets
because no matter what, you lose weight.
Just eat anything and you will
lose weight as long as you eat less.  Even if you only eat edible oils, you
will lose weight if you eat only small amounts.  But now that
that's not what we want, I think that a diet without yo-yu is
ultimately about getting a healthy body
.   I
think that if you set a goal of becoming healthy and develop eating habits, you will be able to create a foundation that is sustainable and can be maintained for a long time.
In that context, you can try all the 50,000 things I've been talking about
.  So, in the case of food,
rather than eating a lot of carbohydrates and fat, which are energy sources like I do, you can eat a low-carb
diet and you
don't need to eat too much fat.  But
now, strength training and cardiopulmonary rehabilitation are
of course good, and cold showers are also
good.
As you go into cold water and take a cold shower, your brown fat
becomes more active, so the
amount of calories you can burn while just breathing while you're still
increases, which is also
good.  yes.
Well, getting enough sleep, eating regularly, and things like that
all help.
In the end, it's all the same story.  It is.
Hello, Garosgil.
Nice to meet you.  I saw that when an A4 person
ate meat, their blood sugar and insulin levels
rose significantly.  This is also what was written in the book
Miracle Restaurant by author Lee Young-hoon, who emphasizes low-carb diets, and
in the book written by Dr. Lee Young-hoon 3
.  hmm.  I do
n't think that's what Doctors 3 claimed, but rather what the
user claimed
.  Do you
know anything about related papers or references?   Should I
take a look and see what I am?  A4
A4
Red Let's just look at it again in the AI ​​series
.
on the ty
mit There's nothing useful here,
um.  yes.  This is the same, and
in the end, it's just an epidemiological
survey.  Is there any basis other than epidemiological research
?
Ah.
I'll expand it a bit so that anyone who's interested can read it too.
[Music]
Hmm.  Oh, I thought this had some kind of meaning
?
[Music]
I'm selling it.  So, what I'm saying is that
people with a lower percentage of fat in Hansu-dae were better off
.  The result.
So, the people who ate less sugar and more fat were
better off.
300 Eat a lot.
อื M. I
think this could be considered an epidemiological investigation.  I haven't read everything, but
here, depending on
how you take the macronutrient ratio, the
A a A4 A4 gene,
so here, it's not just 4, but
2 34,
it seems like they're talking about all of them.  So, we gathered all the people who had 2,
2 3, 2 4, 3 3 4 44
4, and related to the fusion and heterozygous combination, and
after some time, we followed up and looked at the
insulin resistance, that is, the
fasting insulin level, depending on which side had more or less carbohydrates, fat, or protein.
I think they looked at whether fasting insulin was affected by eating a lot or a little of that kind of mass-produced food, so they followed up over time
and
ultimately investigated whether they
had eaten a lot of fat or carbohydrates in the past
.
Well, I think now that it
doesn't really mean anything
.  But
anyway, all the other studies I saw earlier were
only epidemiological studies, but there is
one epidemiological study with the opposite result
.  yes.
Well, there are studies that show that low-carb, high-fat, and high-protein diets have better results.  I
wonder if there is any research that tested the insulin response of people with and without the gene after feeding them meat.  uh.  Oh, I see
you left a comment
.  Oh, is this the YouTube
content?
Oh, this is a thesis.  This
is a paper from 2007.  Can we just
take a quick look at Porongman?  Oh, is there any point in using Google Translate for this
?  Should we try translating it into Diplo Deep
?
hmm.  yes.
Let's look at it in green.
Apolipoprotein 2, encoded by the apolipoprotein 2 gene A42,
plays a key role in the pathogenesis of Alzheimer's disease.  The A4 epsilon 4 variant
is AD, so AD
is the current alchimer.  It is closely related to Alchimer
.  A4 promoter
diversity is also associated with a higher risk of Alzheimer's disease
.
Mouse models of A4 expression have long been used to
elucidate the developmental mechanisms of AD
.
To clarify the role of the A4 gene in Alzheimer's disease, we need to understand how
regulation differs between the mouse G and human A4 genes
and how these differences
affect Alzheimer's risk.
We compared the structure-function of the human A4 gene promoter and
GA4 gene promoter regions
.  The starting probability of the Fairy Warrior is
180p or more, and the
anti-motivation is less than 40%.  Functional
analysis revealed the resemblance of the projector sequence to the
important body, and the human
installation was greatly influenced by the origin of the cell line
.  Similarly, we investigated
nuclear localization with specific HAP and MAP fragments within several cells of various origins and within mouse G.
Although each fragment shares DNA-protein interactions with the others, they are also sensitive to
each other, as recognized by the deletion shift and naming analysis
.  We have identified
possible agreement on these distinct factors
.  The results from the Grand study suggest that the modulation of mouse and
human A4 genes may be sufficiently unique to
quantitatively quantify factors associated with the development of Alcha disease in a
transgenic model of Alcha disease and in a non-therapeutic model of Alcha disease
.  Actually,
I don't know what you're talking about.  yes.   Just
looking at this one, I think I can make it
, oh, this
is a video.  The second thing you told me is,
Mr. Lee Eung, Mr. Hee-mi,
hello.  Oh, you looked for the book
and there are no references, only claims
?  Boy, but honestly,
just making a claim without any reference is
meaningless.  So, it can be used as a reference, but it is
a bit
ambiguous to simply believe it as a high ground.  So, I guess
I need to refer to that and do some more research
.  This is the
same for the book I'm going to write later, and honestly, I
might not have included any references because I find them all bothersome, and I
don't know the exact circumstances of what people are doing. It's
not easy to do each and every one of these things.
But anyway, if it wasn't done,
it would only have a different level of persuasiveness.
There's nothing I can do about this.
Why do you seek the righteousness of Israel
?
Um, I'm not sure what the exact intent of this question is
.  I'm not sure if you're asking why it's non-sterilized milk and
not sterilized milk,
or if you're
asking why non-sterilized milk is good, but why do you sell it? I'm not sure
what you're asking exactly
.   Because I was so
dizzy from walking down the street, I
looked it up and ended up on YouTube
.  I've
been feeling weak and dizzy for a month now, so I've
been checking my diet.  I live by
eating beans and raw beets every day,
so I've always been exposed to oxalic acid.  yes.  This is a part where
high blood pressure improves quickly after following a diet, so
yes, I think it will probably improve quickly if you follow a good diet
.   You
eat a lot of fish and shellfish, right?
Professor Sang-eop Kang of the Department of Chemical and Energy Engineering warned of the dangers of over-consumption of seafood and
urged caution when consuming seafood
.  Seafood in particular
has a lot of internal organs.  I
don't really like seafood, but I was thinking about eating some anchovies, but I
don't feel like eating them.  Is the solvent safe
in the overburden cargo
?  hmm.  First of all, anchovies
are like widows, so I guess fish like anchovies are
also blue-backed fish
?  I'm not sure about that,
but anyway, once you
catch it, it rots and oxidizes really quickly, so you
just cook it right there on the boat
.  I guess it's to stop enzyme activity and things like that
.  So, they just
put them in boiling water right from the boat, and after putting them in boiling water, they take
them out and put them back
in. In the process,
most of them probably use plastic
trays
.  So,
since plastic is being distributed by going in and
out of boiling water, I don't
really want to recommend it in that context
.  And well.  Are
these things Pfa pfas and such found in seafood in such
high amounts that it's a cause for concern?  I don't
know.  I don't think that
amount would be enough to offset the other benefits of seafood
.  But, I don't think you
can have a healthy diet without eating seafood,
so I don't think you
have to eat it unconditionally
.  But
there are some areas that require more attention.  Well,
since it's becoming a bit difficult to compare omega-3 intakes, you'll
need to pay more attention to that part as well.
And yes, diet is
ultimately about that, so the foods we can eat
are set anyway.
So,
rather than saying that there are certain foods you can eat, you
have to eat something.  Because you can't live without eating at all
.
Among the foods I can eat, I need to find the healthiest and most
suitable
foods for me and plan my diet.
What I mean by suitable is biological, so it could be physiologically suitable for my body, but it
could also be taste, price,
difficulty obtaining, accessibility, etc.
So, I need to
consider all of these things comprehensively and
plan my diet
.
We can't not eat at all, we
have to eat something.  But there
may not be 100% perfect foods, and
even if there were, I might not be able to buy them, so animal products, livestock products, that are raised by Joel Salatin
or by incredibly great farmers like Richard Parkins and
raised in really clean environments and in the best possible way,
could be considered almost flawless
.  For example, if that place is now
completely flawless, then let's say the
rest, even if they were pastured in New Zealand or Australia, have
something bad in them
.  So, does that mean we
won't eat the meat produced by Reed Birkins, so we
won't eat it? No, that's not true
.  I have to eat it anyway
.
In that context, it is necessary to make an effort to find the best within the limits of what I can obtain
or within the limits of what I can now eat sustainably and consistently.
In that context, if I
don't eat meat or seafood,
there is no alternative to that anyway
.  I was asking about the overall development issue
.  The discomfort wasn't the only thing,
but there were other reactions as well, and the intensity and
duration were increasing, and I even started shaking my hands, so I
went to see a doctor.  They
made arrangements for me to see my MRI and neurosurgery
.  But it's
over a month until then, and I'm debating whether to stick to cannibalism until then or increase my
carbs like you advised me before
.   For
two years, my diet was a loose, low-carb precedent in many ways
.  Oh,
so you haven't tried what I told you last week
?
Actually, it's not a big deal to eat some carbohydrates
.  yes.  And since you were going to be a bit loose anyway, would
n't it be okay to just try it?  You can try it and
see if it makes you feel better or not, and then
not eat it again
.  Have
you tried increasing your intake of mountain vegetables for a week and
eating things like Mega Mag?
Also, try to consume more electrolytes. Rather than taking calcium, magnesium,
potassium, and other electrolyte
supplements in pill form, try mixing
magnesium and such
in water and drinking them. For
potassium, increase the amount of meat. For calcium, eat
unpasteurized products. If eating unpasteurized
products is difficult, try eating eggshells.
Or, you can boil some bone broth and add vinegar to
it. But if you just eat it like that, it's a bit unclear exactly how much bone broth you're eating, so
I think it would be a good idea to boil it for a while and then chew a certain amount of the softened bones and eat them.
And now let's increase the carbon dioxide content at the same time
.  If I
drink regular milk, which is not digested well by the kidneys,
will unheated milk help with digestion?  hmm.
Normally, raw milk, which is not skimmed,
is much easier to digest.   I
have stage 3 kidney failure and I have to eat animal-based white paper
.  If your kidneys are already in very poor health, we
do not recommend eating a high-protein diet.  So,
people with healthy kidneys won't have
to worry about how much protein they eat, but
people with already poor kidney function are
not recommended to eat a high-protein diet,
so you
should be in an environment where you can continue to get regular checkups and eat well
.  If you ask if you can eat it,
of course you should eat a certain amount.
So, I think that it is not a good idea to eat less than people who are on a regular diet,
whether it is a cannibal diet, a low-fat
diet, or a regular ritual diet
.
Of course, amino acids are a huge
part of protein, but when we eat meat, we don't just
eat those amino acids and protein;
all the vitamins and minerals in the meat are also
important to our body.
In that context, you
need to find an amount that is not a problem and eat it.
Of course, it is
better to not eat things like edible oils or foods that are not good for the kidneys or bones.
Anyway, you need to take care of your calories,
so increase the fat
ratio and eat a lot of fat. When eating lean meat or protein parts, don't just eat muscle meat. Since you can eat less anyway, increase the organ ratio
a little more and eat a little less so that you
can obtain a little more trace minerals
.
Well, oysters
don't have much protein or anything like that, but they are very nutritious,
so they are a type of
shellfish that has a lot of minerals.
And seafood is good,
and it would be helpful to increase the amount of internal organs such as liver, intestines, and kidneys
.
Hello Luna.  I
had a blood test after following the Kanye diet, and my total
cholesterol was high as expected, so I
wasn't too worried, but my bilirubin level
was higher than usual.  I looked it up and it
says it's related to liver disease.
Could it be that the protein-rich liver is
damaged?
I don't think so.  Excessive protein intake raises a
slight question as to whether you have consumed excessive protein in the first place
.  I'm not sure how much you ate
.  Well, as for protein,
unless you have kidney failure or other kidney health issues like the other person who asked a question a little while ago, there can be no protein excess in the first place, even
if there is a fat deficiency
.
As far as I know.  yes.
I don't think that's why.  I think there must be some other
reason
.  Oh, I'm a 52kg woman and I
eat about 500g of meat, 40g of liver, and three eggs a day.  yes.
If you have that protein, it's not an excess, it's a deficiency
.  Yes, there is no choice.  Such
excess.  There is no such thing as excess, but even
if there were such a thing, since you are
concerned about that,
I would say you ate 40g of liver and three eggs for 500g.  That excess is
ridiculous.
Can I just supplement with Vitamin K2 and D3 for my Carnivore supplement?
That might not be necessary either.
Also, although it's called cannibalism,
each person's cannibalism
varies greatly. For example, for vitamin D3,
people who go outside and get a lot of sunlight separately from their diet
don't need to supplement. For
vitamin K2, if you have a lot of poultry such as
eggs and chicken in your cannibalism diet, you do
n't need to take it separately.
If you don't eat any liver and only eat lean meat, you may
need to take vitamin A additionally.  And maybe,
and
other than that, in the long run,
things like manganese are quite difficult to obtain from meat unless you eat mussels
.  I guess I
'll have to eat it with the bones and stuff.  But
there are some people who don't eat things like bones.   If you
don't eat bones, don't eat dairy, and really
don't eat any of these types of calcium sources,
then you might
need to take a calcium supplement, even though they say it's not recommended
.  And now, depending on the person, there
may be a vitamin C deficiency
.  Because we can no longer eat meat from animals that are relatively rich in vitamin C like we used to
.
Well, other than that,
there are a few other things that can come into play.
Minerals are also like that. In the past,
before agriculture, especially the modern era, began with extremely intensive farming, the
meat of animals
had much more minerals than it does now. So,
even if you eat the same amount of meat now, you may
need to supplement with mega-minerals or other minerals because you may be lacking in minerals.
Even if I say I'm a carnivore,
for example, I should eat about 1 kg of meat, but
if I can only eat 500 g or 400 g, then I may be lacking that much more and need to
supplement with other things
.  So
this is a bit
ambiguous.  People say that the diet is carnivore,
but in reality, carnivore is a very rough
concept.  If you only eat animal products and
do not eat the 10 plant-based foods, you
fall into the category of carnivore. However, it is
a bit
ambiguous because not everything that falls into the category of carnivore is healthy.  Resolution of my orthostatic hypotension and low
iron levels was one
of the quickest changes I noticed with my diet
.  yes.   That's why, if you
have iron deficiency, you
often just get prescribed iron supplements.  But
to metabolize iron in our body, we also need vitamin A and
copper
.  But you can never get vitamin A and
copper just by eating lean meat
.  You absolutely
have to eat liver.  Yes, the liver
contains a lot of copper and vitamin A.  It
is a special treatment for iron deficiency, but it is not helpful to
just eat a lot of iron supplements, especially since it is not heme iron and is difficult to absorb.
It will only make you feel bad and not help.
hmm.  Are there any
foreign YouTube channels that I can watch and study or learn about liturgy or cannibalism
?  Or are there any
foreign health-related YouTube
channels that you enjoy?
Actually, lately I haven't been
studying much by watching YouTube channels diligently
.  But the channel I watched a lot was
EO Nutrition, which is
run by Ellie Overton.
That was also
good because it organized the technical parts really well, and this person is also fun.  Of course this is
a bit like, I'm not saying it's 100% about diet,
but yeah,
what's that person's name?   You're
standing there.
What is the name of the millionaire who spends tens of billions or hundreds of billions of won a year to live a long and healthy life without dying?  I think Brian did something
.  That guy who's being criticized right now is
Brian
Johnson.  Oh anyway, this person's channel is
really fun too.  It's well organized and the
experiments are really fun
.  hmm.
[Music]
And I watched this guy's channel quite a bit
.  High
Intensities.  I think he's still doing it these days
. This person is
sharing a lot of the latest research papers and
talking about various things
. Yes.   I really
like this guy too.  There is also a Bolseradi channel
.
But these days, I do
n't really know how to upload videos.
[Music]
And who else is there?
This is the Ionution I mentioned earlier. This
guy is also really
good.  yes.  I think the person I would like to recommend is
me
right now
.  yes.  All the people I just showed you are
really good.
What do you think about the idea that plants can be removed by assembly?  Well,
there are actually a lot of ways to remove it, and
I've introduced a lot of them.   If you
watch my videos, you'll see that it
was a special episode for the first full moon of the lunar year, with some stories about how to neutralize pituitary glands and other things.
I made a video of the process of making healthy noodles with the noodles made of crispy bread.  Oh, and other than that,
when I was writing about traditional diets, I
also introduced how Africans neutralized and ate all kinds of seeds, nuts, and other things that they used to eat
.  yes.
But one thing you need to know now is that
not all plant toxins can be treated with just one method.
As there are many types of plant toxins, there are different
ways to neutralize each toxin.
For example, in peat,
there is an enzyme called phytase that breaks down phytic acid.  The principle is to activate the enzyme called phytase and
neutralize the peat contained in the seeds of the plant
.
This is a neutralization method. It involves
soaking the seeds in lukewarm water,
soaking them in a slightly acidic solution, and soaking them in something like that.
Even if phytase is activated in this way, there are seeds or offerings that have insufficient phytate compared to the amount of phytate they contain
.  Even
though they are called the same,
not all phytates are completely broken down. They have to be mixed with
other grains that have more phytates than the phytic acid they already have and
go through other processes such as being soaked
.  So, even if it is the same phytic acid,
it is not resolved by just calling it the same.  Those rye
things, they have a lot of pita bread.
What was it?
I don't remember exactly.  Anyway,
there are other types of grains or seeds that have a lot of phytate, but not much phytate.
They
can't neutralize Pisan just by calling them alone
.
And, the amount of fat can be reduced to some extent by calling it that way
or by cooking it, but
in the case of a neck injury, if you just call it that way
and cook
it and eat it all, it
doesn't really reduce that much.  In order to remove oxalic acid, in the
case of pit-line, it was
broken down by an enzyme called peterhazy, but
oxalic acid cannot be broken down and
must be physically removed.
In the process of physically removing it, water-
soluble substances are often used, so usually boiling them in water,
blanching them, steaming them, or other such methods
are used.  But now, when you boil it in water, it comes out in the water,
so the heat
doesn't destroy it, it just dissolves in the water
.  Okseolsan Mountain.
So, if I drink all of this water after boiling it, it means I am
drinking all of the oxalate, so it has no meaning.
After boiling, you have to pour out the water, and
when boiling, you have to boil it for quite a long time.
In some cases, a lot of water comes out, and this
varies depending on the food. In the
case of spinach, it is said that if you boil it for about 15 minutes, it will
reduce by 50%
.  But, even if
spinach is boiled for 15 minutes, it is
no longer edible, and
even if it is reduced by 50%, there are still
too many oxygen atoms.  So,
when you boil it, the amount of oxalic acid decreases to some extent.  This is
true, but does that mean you can
eat all the products that contain a lot of oxalic acid just by boiling them?
That is not true either.
Lectins are also destroyed when cooked under high pressure as the
temperature becomes extremely high
.  But
there are some that cannot be destroyed.
If you ferment it, there are some that become neutralized
.  Some lectins are now broken down
.  But
there are some that resist fermentation.  So, since there are
so many types of lectins,
examples are a bit ambiguous.
For example, gluten lectin
is a type of lectin, and even if you use regular yeast to
make commercial bread, it is very fine, so you can
bake the bread and do it right away.  Anyway,
despite that, the lectin gluten is
not broken down at all.
If you eat it, you will die immediately if you eat it from a cell-stimulating disease patient
.  But now,
in the case of a really well-made Saudo,
there are cases where even people with cellulitis can take it and it is okay.
To that extent, there is a
huge difference in being able to decompose the gluten to that extent. I
have experienced the same thing of baking and discarding for 5 minutes, but there
can be a big difference to that extent.
Even if you make it in a similar way, and even if you
ferment it properly or
use similar methods,
there are still some gluten that cannot be neutralized.
For example, the
lectins in eggplant vegetables are not destroyed by heat or
by direct contact.  So,
things like red pepper powder and
things like so-called red pepper paste that are fermented and eaten are all useless.  The lectins
remain intact.  But of course,
now that
this is that, if I were to
tell you more about plant toxins, well,
there are actually not just one or two,
but there are a ton of
them, but they don't
cause problems to everyone at the same level
.  Some people
can handle certain plant toxins with relative ease,
while others can be incredibly sensitive to others
.  This varies greatly from person to person
.  So, on the other hand, if we
look at it from the most consequential perspective, it may be most important to be
able to identify plant toxins that I am sensitive to
.   There are
things that I can handle quite well, things that I
enjoy eating and things that add joy and vitality to my life,
so I
don't necessarily have to not eat them.  Well,
even if it's not a good thing, just from a health standpoint
.  But we
don't live with just that.  yes.  Well, that's
true.  Hello, Plow.   I
saw in the video that your blood test results showed that you ate too much butter, which resulted in very high triglyceride levels.
How much butter did you eat?  I'm curious.  yes.
I don't remember the exact details of the blood test results because the video is a bit
old
.  It's probably been 4 or 5 years
.  yes.  But
if I were to say that I ate a lot of boats, I would say that I probably
ate at least 225g a day
.  I could have eaten more.   I
would have eaten half of a big 454g or 500g block of butter.  For protein, just eat meat
.  Oh, the hand is still there.
Mr. Dromi
.  Oh, yes.
There's more chatting than I thought, so I'll
go down and read it quickly
.  I bought a
nutritional supplement to take with my yellow food
.  How much Molly Unit should I
consume per day?  The
nutritional supplement I bought said it contained 400 mg per serving
.  Actually, I don't know
much about the recommended dosage or anything like that
.  yes.
I think it would be better to just eat it with the liver.
There are a lot of olives in the liver, so you probably won't have to worry about
eating too much when eating it as a food
.  I watched a lot of the broadcast last week, but
there was no reaction with any symptoms.  Mega Mag ordered and
waiting.   If
adding carbohydrates doesn't seem to have any effect and
taking electrolytes does
n't seem to have any effect, then yes,
I think it would be a good idea to get tested.
If the problem cannot be solved by eating carbohydrates, I wonder if it is necessary to continue eating carbohydrates
.  If you are
just worried and
want to improve your diet a little,
then it would be better to go with a strict cannibal diet
.   I
was listening to a YouTube video by Volsladiner, and it
seemed like you were talking about the negative aspects of intermittent fasting. I'm
not very good at English, so I don't think I understood it well
. I wonder if you know anything about this and if you've heard it, what are your thoughts?  no see.   I
think that there has been a bit of a change in the trend of intermittent fasting, but this is
n't a recent trend.  It's
been about a year or two, maybe two years
.  In the past, before that, you and
I would all praise and worship the fast
.
But now this is what people think, in my opinion
.  Intermittent fasting
is so easy.
In fact, if you say that you don't have to eat because you're busy, then you can say that you do
n't have to eat much all day, and
if you shorten the time you eat and eat
in short bursts like this, and
if you reduce the time you spend eating during the day, many
modern people feel it's convenient and even
free, so
I think they don't have much difficulty following it.  But now the problem is,
for example, if a person who used to eat breakfast, lunch, and dinner now
only eats breakfast and lunch, or lunch and dinner, he or she has to
eat the rest of the meal well since he or she missed that one meal, but I think that
part is not as good as expected
.  hmm.
So, I think that as
more and more people just starve, there are some negative side effects that come with it
.
Anyway, in the long run,
eating a low-calorie diet,
eating less, and just extending the fasting period is
not very good.  The reason I
don't recommend 1-day meals is
because of that context. For example, even if you compress your
time and eat like intermittent fasting, such as eating 2 meals in January, even
if you eat both meals, you
can still eat
insufficiently and not be able to eat the important amount of each meal that you
need.
I personally think that these aspects are more problematic now.   I
think that if you eat enough even if you eat two meals, you will hardly ever experience the problems that those people worry about.  Because even if we're not
completely on these,
there are a lot of things we can get a glimpse of through other related studies, but if you
eat a lot of that protein at once, it
used to be like a lot of rumors
floating around.  Since the amount of protein we can absorb at one time
is only about 30g,
eating more than that is meaningless,
so we need to eat it often.  You should
n't eat all this stuff at once, you
should share it.  There used to be a
lot of baseless rumors like this city gossip, but
recently, research has revealed that
even if you eat 100g of protein, equivalent to 500g of meat, at a time, you can maintain muscle protein synthesis over a long
period of time while the blood
amino acid concentration is high
.  What that means is that if we
eat a lot, the amount we eat will
continue to circulate in the blood and maintain the
state of eating, such as synthesizing muscle
proteins.
So,
when
we do a strong fast, there is no reason to experience problems like staying in a bond for too long
.
Structurally.  So in that context,
I don't think intermittent fasting itself is the
problem.
It's that by doing intermittent fasting, you're
compressing your eating time, so you
eat breakfast and lunch, or lunch and
dinner, or skipping one path, but the
time between meals becomes shorter,
so you have to eat a lot in between those shortened meal times, so you have to eat
two meals. But because the
time between meals is short, you
say, "I'm full, I can't eat," and eat less.
And
because of that long-term brainwashing, there are many people, especially women, who are trying to lose weight, who
eat
less and feel proud of themselves, even though they know that theoretically they should eat more.
I think it might be a bit bad in that case.
No, it's not that. Just eat two meals, but if you
eat two meals to your heart's content and
eat enough, I think you won't have to worry about being a manager
.
Did you know that Dr. Seol praised you?  Oh, you sent me that capture,
and someone
uploaded it to the KakaoTalk chatroom, so I
saw it.  yes.
How many eggshells should I eat a day to survive 80 years
?  If I boil the shell and chew
it, is it safe to eat it?   You
only need to take about 2g.
Since it is calcium carbonate, if you look at the molecular weight and such, you
can see that roughly half of it is calcium.  So, taking just 2g
is enough.  You don't have to eat much
.  Of course, if you boil it and use it, it
is safe.  When I make scrambled
eggs, I just roughly break them up like this,
cut them into pieces like this,
put them in, and scramble them together.
Then, now, when you eat, you misread it a little
.  Hello, Daze.
Do you sometimes eat lamb or beef kidney?   I have
n't eaten it recently, it's been a while.   I
used to eat it often.  Hello, Lee Do-hyun
.  I
heard someone ask about protein in stage 3 renal failure.
My child has stage 4 renal failure.
As you said, I don't eat a lot of protein.
What about butter or eggs with fatty organs?
I would like to request an answer sheet for my disappearance.  yes.
Anyway, you need to continue to get tested and
closely monitor how you are reacting to this diet and
adjust accordingly
.  So, I think it is absolutely necessary to have a thorough examination with the doctor, as
if he were doing a good job
.  I think you should share with your doctor that you are trying this
type of diet, even
though he or she may not like it
.  yes.  Anyway, I think it would be
good to try it now
.  I think it would be difficult for me to not eat at all
.  So, I think
it's a bit too difficult to have a low body temperature and recover without eating any nutrients at all
.  Hello, Lee Hyuk-pal.
Hello, Song Songi.  If the shell trial is
blocked,
would it be good if it came without any problems?  I'm giving it to my kids as a snack,
but I don't think it's good for their health.
Well, it
might not be that rotten and bad
.   I
eat stir-fried small anchovies every day.
Is there a problem with excessive intake of certain nutrients when eating them frequently?  Or maybe it's the
issue of exposure to pollutants.  As I mentioned earlier,
plastic anchovies are cooked right after they are caught and
then cooked on the boat. Now, whether they are cooked on the boat
or brought back to Korea, they are
heated in a plastic tray and then caught with that and
put in hot water,
so I don't think that's very good
.   If the
amount is too large, you
may end up consuming too much calcium.
Where can I get my vitamins and minerals if I don't eat vegetables and herbs?
Nutritional supplements Actually, plants and such, that is,
plant-based foods or vegetables and
greens,
do not contain many vitamins and minerals.
As much as you think about it, you won't just take my word for it. If you just
do a quick search, you'll find
that if you take any beef, or liver, or mackerel,
or any fish you're familiar with, and then you
take a small intestine, and
then you take something like beef sirloin, and you
compare the nutritional information of any of the so-called superfoods and plants, and
there's no comparison.  If you just
eat a lot of meat, you
can get all the vitamins and minerals.
I have
researched and written down some things on my blog before,
so if I may show you one of them briefly,
when I was talking about the liturgical diet, I wrote a part 2 of the Eskimo diet where you don't have to
eat vegetables.
Here, you can see the nutritional content of so-called
superfoods such as broccoli,
kale, carrots, and mackerel
, salmon roe
, and sardines.
From top to bottom, it shows vitamin A, vitamin
D3, vitamin B6, B12, vitamin
C, folic acid, phosphorus, iron, niacin, copper,
iodine, and omega 3
.  Aside from this, the same goes for vitamins,
B vitamins, and other things
.  well.  What else
is there?
This is the case with most minerals, and for example,
magnesium is found in greater amounts in plant-based foods,
but the
bioavailability is much higher in animal-based foods, so the
difference is not as great as the indicated amount
.  But anyway,
in that context, in the case of magnesium, I
would recommend supplementing a little more with something like Mega Mag.  yes.   Yes,
that's right.  Except for vitamin C,
most people
eat more meat.
I
was 150 km/h and 50 km/h at Seoul National University, but
there was nothing special about the prescription. After 2 years, I was on dialysis. Another natural healing
hospital recommended brown rice tea and other plant-based protein. I
lost 78 km/h and my
hair fell out a lot, so I was worried and
felt very bad.   I would
like to ask you some questions about the city walls.  Yes,
I think it's the same story as what I said earlier.
Among my videos,
there is one introducing PalioMedina.  Well,
there's a video about this,
but Palemedina has a diet called the
Paleolytic Ketogenic Diet, or PKD, that's now being used for therapeutic purposes
.  This is
now a very strict diet
and may differ slightly
from the typical carnivore diet.
But one of the characteristics of this paleo PKD is that it does
not contain a lot of protein.
Rather,
it is very little.  So instead of these picks, the
fat percentage is incredibly high.
The ratio of fat to protein is
calculated by weight, gram for gram, of fat
.  It's not a calorie ratio, it's just
by weight, so I eat 2 parts fat and
1 part protein
.  So, the ratio of pure protein to
pure fat is 1 for protein and 2 for fat
.  If you
break this down into calorie percentages, you can see that 20% of calories come from protein and
80% come from fat
.  To that extent, it is now a very high-
fat diet.  So, with
this, we are now treating cancer and various
autoimmune diseases and such,
so I think it would be better to use an approach that is closer to this type of diet
.
As for the exact ratio and such,
even if they have the same kidney failure, it will
vary from person to person. Some
people may be able to eat a little more, and
some may need to eat a little less. You
can start with a very small amount and gradually increase it over time.
Now, for accurate consulting on these things, it
would be best to contact them directly or ask Paledina. Yes, that would be the best, of course
.  yes.  But even if that's not the case, I
still think it would be good to keep the diet itself similar in composition
.  As I told someone else,
rather than increasing the amount of lean meat, since the
amount of protein you can eat
is limited anyway, you should
not just eat beef or sirloin as much as possible, but rather eat more nutritious
parts,
such as shellfish or seafood. If you eat animal meat, you
should eat some of it.  But now,
rather than eating only 100% meat, you should try to
increase the proportion of liver and other things as much as possible, and also
eat a lot of things like kidneys, bone marrow, and brain that have a high fat content
.  yes.
Minerals and vitamins are sensitive to heat, so is it possible to
obtain them completely from cooked foods
?
First of all, it is not true that minerals are weak against heat
.
So, of course, now, not all types of
minerals are
100% absorbed when you just put them in your mouth. It's
important to know how they are absorbed and what their bioavailability is, but fundamentally,
minerals
cannot be destroyed by heat.  So, at the level where we
do general cooking
.  So,
in order to destroy the mineral or make it not a mineral, you have to
do something like nuclear fission or nuclear fusion
.  That's why the
minerals themselves
cannot be destroyed by heat when we cook
.  But now,
when cooking, you grill things like meat.
Then the juices will drain out.   When we
say that something is leaking out, we mean that
something inside is coming out, and that there is a
loss of something that is physically moving.
Some water-soluble vitamins are
lost through the juice, but now minerals such as potassium are
lost a lot
.  So, if you continue to lose meat juice,
throw away all the juice, and
eat only what's left, your
intake of minerals, including potassium, will inevitably decrease
.  There is that part
.  But if not, then you
don't have to worry about minerals being destroyed by heat or anything like that
.  Not all vitamins are
sensitive to heat.  You can see that the most heat-sensitive
thing is vitamin B6
.
Some are destroyed when cooked,
and some are changed to prevent absorption, so you can
assume that about half of them are unusable
.
Oh, but other than that, for
things like the B vitamins,
you can see that they decrease by about 20% to 30%, and
fat-soluble vitamins like vitamins A, D, and K2 are relatively
heat-stable, but K2
is sensitive to light, so
if you dry it in the sun or something like that,
most of it will be destroyed
.  yes.  Well, anyway,
that's it.  yes.  Anyway,
to get more vitamin B6, I recommend
grilling your steak medium rare
.  So, I made a video
about why you should eat less medium-sized meat
.  Yes,
there is a video here, so I hope you watch it too
.  I think eating raw food is
somewhat good, because
every culture in the world
has some kind of eating habit that involves eating raw food
.  It's the same for us and for other
countries, wherever we go?
Oh, it's
a study room.  The cafe that Hee-mi runs
and my cafe used to
have a group chat room, but almost
all of it was moved to Hee-mi's chat room
.  You can just search here and
come in.
This is it.  Yes,
there is a KakaoTalk group called “Let’s study together like this.”
It's an open chat room.  If you come to our cafe, you will
see that the link needs to be
changed, but I think you may still be
accessing my KakaoTalk room and then moving on from there
.  Well, you
can do that, but if you just
do that search, it will come up.  The
password will probably be written down if you scroll down like this
.  yes.   If you
look here, you can see that the notice has all the guides
.  yes.  Carnivore Immun Guide
organized in Notion.  Hee-mi
has organized it like this.  And they
answer questions like this
.  yes.   Since
there is more than one person, I think it would be good to go and
chat a bit and get some things out of it
.  Ja.
Hello everyone.  Oh,
if I write this as a link open chat room,
will it get cut off?  Is there a
difference in the quality of carbohydrates and sleep because of the censorship on YouTube
?  How many carbohydrates do
you eat per day?  Do you feel the biggest difference in your sleep compared to when you eat a lot of carbohydrates
?
Oh, no.
I don't know for sure, I haven't measured it properly, but I
just feel it personally
.  When to eat carbohydrates and
when not to eat carbohydrates.  There are many times when I don't eat carbohydrates, and
there are many times when I eat them, but I
don't really pay attention to it.  I
need to eat some carbonated drinks.  Or maybe I
shouldn't eat it.  Oh, but now,
even though I think I'm gaining weight,
sometimes I
intentionally eat more just to eat more calories,
but these days, if you
want to eat carbohydrates, you have
to do something else.  I
have to cook that meal anyway, but I'm
a bit lazy right now, so I'm in the
process of moving and I'm busy with work, so things
haven't been sorted out yet, so I'm not eating for one person
.  But yeah,
anyway,
I don't think I can really feel the difference in quality of sleep.  These days, James Didical
is also in the Cannibal Community and WWE because he said that eating too much protein in X causes acidity.
Oh, but if you're worried about acidification, why
don't you just eat a lot of protein and some fruit?   I'm not
sure why you're cutting back on protein
.  So, meat
doesn't just contain protein, so I'd like to talk about why those parts
are like that
.  I must have felt a cold that I didn't like
.  well.  But,
as you said, when you
can't metabolize fat, your
blood sugar drops, you
feel like you lack energy, and when you're
in a state of shock, like hypoglycemia,
don't you feel like you're going to faint?
Try eating a spoonful of honey before going to bed
.
Hello, Shinnabro.  What time is the live broadcast?  Well,
usually on Monday evenings.  Yesterday, I
couldn't broadcast because I had a bit of a misunderstanding due to moving
.  Between pepper powder and cinnamon powder,
which would you choose as a seasoning?
But aren't the two roles too similar?
So,
don't you think that evacuation and pepper are somewhat interchangeable?
Well, if you have to use one anyway,
Baekhoo powder
isn't too bad.  There isn't much oxalic acid either.  Well,
there's no piperine and there are other things, but
anyway,
Baek-hoo is much
better than Heuk-gu-chu.  Although dog skin contains a lot of oxalic acid, it
is insoluble, so if you only
think about that, it may not be that bad
.   Because I'm
not going to eat much.  What kind of fruit can I eat
?
Most fruits are fine.
It's good if you drink it with 6% alcohol, but if you don't drink it with 6% alcohol,
what
was that 1% baking soda?
I think it was probably a 1% solution.
2% baking soda. 2% isn't bad either, so you can just use
2% to be safe, or
you can try 1.5%. If you
just soak it in water mixed with that amount,
most of the pesticides on the surface will be neutralized since they are acidic
.  yes.  Since most of it disappears, if it
's not organic, it would be
better to neutralize any pesticides before eating it, right?  yes.  You
can do that and drink the overheating that suits you best.
There seem to be a lot of people who don't have any particular discomfort but find that bananas and citrus fruits are not so good for them
.  yes.  Well, anyway, that's it.   If
I eat too much of something like mango, I
get an upset stomach.   If you
eat too many bananas, you will feel
sick.  yes.  Well, anyway, it varies from person to person
.  I
'm eating cod roe with cinnamon oil, but should I avoid it because of the oxalic acid
?  There is no oxalic acid in the 5th day of synergy
.  That oxalic acid is water soluble, so it's
not present in those types of oils.  I
am a man in my 50s and
have been eating sirloin bone soup and raw fish for several years, but I have
frequent recurrences of moderate risk.  I
barely eat carbs, but every year I get the dreaded "pre-diabetes" day
.  I wonder if it's important because the sugar content is a bit high
?  Should I
eat liver more often
?  hmm.   The fact that you
don't drink much water may be due to the degree to which you
don't drink it, which
may have created physiological insulin resistance in your body.  So, instead of tea,
try to consistently consume about 50g of carbohydrates per day.   I
think it would be a good idea to consistently eat about 100g of carbohydrates, for example, 50g per day, and then take a blood test again after eating for about a month
.  And pre-diabetes
isn't just about blood sugar levels.  You probably
saw that fossil too.
If you think about the hemoglobin level, in fact,
once the fasting blood sugar level drops, you should
check it by eating some carbohydrates for about a month or two weeks.
And of course, it
takes about three months for the glycated pigment to go down, but you can't call it
pre-diabetes just because of the glycated pigment
.  Of course,
now it seems like your actual blood sugar level is high,
but the glycation pigment literally
assumes that red blood cells will only live for 3 months and the
study is done on that basis,
but if you do cannibalism or some other
diet, the red blood cells may live a little longer, and if
the red blood cells live a long time, as it is
literally a long time, the
glycated ones may increase and the
results may be a little ambiguous
.  And if you
don't exercise, it would be good to do strength training regularly
.  As exercise for children, I have them
walk barefoot on a nearby mountain for about an hour and a half
.  I saw
something connected to the bed because other exercises were too difficult
.  Oh yes.  But actually,
I think it's much more effective to actually go out into nature and do it than to do it like this in bed.  That's why I do
n't know what this is.  So, as I said in the earthing
video,
people who try to explain earthing scientifically
talk a lot about free electrons and this and that, but if you just
look at that, you
should see the same effect even if you earth it in a water pipe or in your house. And you don't have to take your shoes
off, you should see the same effect if you just go in naturally
.  But there's something about this
.  So, I
don't think this is something that really follows the natural path, and
I think there must be a
scientific reason behind it, even though it hasn't been explained yet
.  But we
don't know exactly what it is yet.
But
anyway, even I and
those who didn't really think much about earthing in the first place, and those who thought that earthing was just like that even if you tried
other diets and stuff, and
those who
didn't feel like it was a placebo or anything like that, there are
so many people who have experienced effects that were so effective that you wonder if it makes sense almost immediately after actually doing earthing, so
there's definitely something there.
But I think there is something that cannot be smoked by using things like grounding rods inside the house,
such as water pipes,
gas pipes, or connecting wires from outside
.  Of course,
now they are completely ineffective.  I
don't mean to say that,
but I think there's something there.
If you watch that documentary about Earthing, there's a guy named
Clint Ober who's been
spreading the word about Earthing. In
that documentary, there's a
story about how when a
child in the Native American tribe gets
sick, even though they're people who almost always do
Earthing all the time and do
n't have anything else to do, they
make a campfire and
dig a hole in the ground and have the baby sit in the hole all day
.  So,
I don't really know.  What is this?
From the Earth's perspective, even if you
dig a hole 1 meter deep,
it's nothing.
I didn't even go in.  But those people,
of course, now it is not known whether they really went into the pit and
brought it out,
but they believed that it had some kind of healing
effect, and they would keep them
in the pit for hours and days like that until they got better
.  I'm not sure if this
is an effect that black brings, or if it's something like free electrons or
something like that
.  But I
feel like there's something there.
Would it be okay for my child with kidney failure to eat at least some fruit?
But, when you are receiving treatment, it
may be better not to eat fruit
.
So, I would recommend that you try a more
strict PKD-like cannibal
diet if possible
.  Well,
if it's difficult to go straight ahead, you should try going step by step
.  Of course, it is
better to not eat vegetables at all than to just eat vegetables, and
if you eat plants, fruits
are better.  Fruits are, to some extent,
made for plants to eat
.  Well, there are cases where the target
is not human and is harmful to humans, but is
okay for the target who wants to be eaten
.  And
actually, it wasn't made with our health in mind,
so it's not like it's
good for our health
.
Well, it's a bit different from the usual one where there's no problem
.  It's like this.  I will
now finish the broadcast by reading this to the very end
.
You've talked about quite a lot of different things.  hmm.   It's a
good product, but once you buy it, it
looks good.  I don't think it's bad.
yes.  Well, that fun alternative is now
to share it in the KakaoTalk room where we were studying Cannibalism earlier.  I'm going to finish the broadcast and
go to bed.
hmm.  yes.  I'm not sure about next week
or the week after that
.
I'll update you again next week.  Thank you
for watching and seeing how it goes
.  yes.  I will work hard again
.  I'll
get it next week.  Please click like once
.